# SIMONE GREEN

in www.linkedin.com/in/green-simone/ sgreen2302.github.io

# **ABOUT ME**

Soon-to-be computer science graduate with a passion for investigating the intersection of technology and geopolitics through cybersecurity analysis, concentrated on nation-state threat actors. I have experience in cyber threat intelligence in the context of tool development and analytical applications within the financial sector.

#### Skills

**Programming Languages:** Python, Java/JavaScript/JSON, HTML/CSS, C, OCaml, SQL, JQL, Bash, ARM/RISC-V Assembly Language

Tools & Frameworks: MITRE ATT&CK, Kali Linux, Wireshark, Splunk, Anomali, Command Line, Pandas, Jira, Git, Agile

#### Honors

Bowers CIS Distinguished Leadership in Service Award APRIL 2023

Code2040 Finalist FEBRUARY 2022

Executive Leadership Council Moody's Ray McDaniel Scholar MARCH 2021

Comcast Leaders & Achievers Scholar MAY 2020

NCWIT Aspirations in Computing Awardee FEBRUARY 2020

## **Affiliations**

**Grace Hopper Conference (GHC)** SEPTEMBER 2023

**Rewriting the Code (RTC)** MAY 2022 - PRESENT

Women in Cybersecurity (WiCyS) DECEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

ColorStack

AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT

# **EDUCATION**

Cornell University, College of Engineering, Ithaca, NY MAY 2024 B.S. in Computer Science **GPA**: 3.7 (Dean's List)

Minors in Information Science and Law & Society

Relevant Courses: Objected Oriented/Functional Programming & Data Structures Computer System Organization • Operating Systems • Statistics • Discrete Structures Information Ethics, Law, and Policy • Cybersecurity Law and Policy • Cyberwarfare

**DIS: Study Abroad in Scandinavia**, Copenhagen, Denmark Study Abroad Program in Computer Science, Political Science, and Law

JAN - MAY 2023 **GPA**: 4.0

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Undergraduate Teaching Assistant, Cornell Bowers, Ithaca, NY

JULY 2022 - PRESENT

- Assist in general organization, communications, and grading for Computer System Organization course of 350+ students.
- Co-lead weekly lab section of 40 students and host weekly office hours to reinforce content and
- Act as a liaison between course staff and the Engineering Learning office to direct content for supplemental courses.

# Cyber Threat Intelligence Intern, BlackRock, Wilmington, DE

JUNE 2023 - AUGUST 2023

- · Contributed to 5 threat monitoring reports under weekly deadlines for information, which prompted actionable next steps presented to an audience of 70+ cybersecurity professionals and leaders.
- Implemented action plans to address phishing and brand-related threats identified using Splunk and DomainTools and pitched them to senior leadership.
- Gathered requested intelligence for incident response analysts and provided support for ongoing investigations via Proofpoint, Flashpoint, and Recorded Future.

#### Global Technology Analyst Intern, Bank of America, Charlotte, NC JUNE 2022 - AUGUST 2022

- Maintained UI/UX and backend platforms for the Digital Platform technology team, employing a Kanban Agile workflow.
- Applied functional changes to auto loan applications using NodeJS and Git to adhere to ADA
- Managed portfolios to streamline code releases and audited current projects within the Merchant Services team using Jira.

#### Cybersecurity Intelligence Intern, The MITRE Corporation, Remote JUNE 2021 - MAY 2022

- Applied organizational changes to 42 techniques within the MITRE ATT&CK enterprise framework input to increase usability and readability.
- Authored and led research into 3 new sub-techniques utilized by global threat actors under the Defense Evasion tactic.
- Identified a new sub-technique, Double File Extension, within the Masquerading technique while investigating APTs correlated with Phishing and published this addition to the framework as part of the October 2021 release of ATT&CK.

## **EXTRACURRICULARS**

**Theta Tau Professional Engineering** Fraternity - Kappa Delta Chapter Diversity & Inclusion Chair

SEPTEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

**National Society of Black Engineers** 

General Body Member SEPTEMBER 2021 - PRESENT **Underrepresented Minorities in Computing** (URMC)

Former Executive Board - Outreach Chair AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT

Alpha Phi Omega Service Fraternity Event Planner FEBRUARY 2021 - PRESENT